

Brandon Distler

bdistler83@gmail.com | 502-594-1962 | Louisville, Kentucky

Summary

Highly-motivated employee with technical skills, a desire to take on new challenges. Strong work ethic, adaptability, and exceptional interpersonal skills. Adept at working effectively unsupervised and quickly mastering new skills.

Skills & Areas of Expertise

Network Infrastructure and Topology | Router and Modem Install | Tier 1, 2, and 3 Customer Support | Troubleshooting Phone, Internet, and Cable Issues | Python | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Reporting & Performance Analytics | Resource Allocation & Schedule Management

Professional Experience

Spectrum Communications | Workforce Management | March 2015 - Current

- Manage 500 plus technician's schedules and allocate technical resources providing timely customer support achieving prompt availability
- Prioritize customer issues by severity, urgency, and technician availability to keep availability within 2 days.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams on special projects including: (list a couple projects)
- Served as a key stakeholder configuring and managing the implementation and roll out of new markets for the dispatch call center
- Created SOPs (standard operating procedures) to ensure consistent and high-quality execution achieving a XX% improvement in arrival time accuracy/achievement and technician calendar accuracy

Spectrum Communications | Routing Coordinator | June 2014 to March 2015

- Managed scheduling and logistics for Technicians while maintaining a consistent workflow
- Analyzed and assigned most effective routes to serve current customer needs
- Responded to customer escalations regarding scheduling needs and conflicts
- Prioritized and organized tasks to efficiently accomplish service goals
- Modified existing software systems to enhance performance and add new features

Time Warner Cable | Technical Support Representative | June 2011 - June 2014

- Provided direct support to customers through Help Desk regarding TWC products
- Presented basic troubleshooting for internet, phones, physical connections, software issues; proficient knowledge of Microsoft, Apple, and Android operating systems
- Strong ability to troubleshoot network, computer and email issues; Outlook and Apple mail
- Exposure to DNS, DHCP and TCP/IP; knowledge of routers, modems, switches, and hubs

Education and Training

Sullivan College of Technology And Design | Associate of Science in Information Security and Computer Forensics